Oh, look, it's about freakin' time.
Oh, hey. What's up, Kasha Wazaki?
Call me Senna. Gah.
Uh, you call Harpy Face by her first name, don't you?
But for whatever reason, you feel the need to squeeze out five syllables
when you wanna talk to me.
Okay, fine.
Hey, Senna.
Can we just get this show on the road already?
Right. Mikazu...
It's Yozara.
Okay. Yozara.
Hm.
So, how does this club even work?
We're just supposed to make friends even though none of us know town?
Oh, I know one way of making friends. Video games. Hm.
so you want us to make friends with gamers now because why don't be so judgmental gaming has
gone way beyond mainstream check it out I've got a PSP plan of attack are you serious my
little sister has that last night when I went out to dinner by myself you went out to eat alone shut
up anyway four guys from school were sitting at the table behind me and they were all playing this
game together nice monster hunting have you played it no but it's your basic fantasy RPG you get to hunt
monsters but the cool thing is you have the ability to play with other people at the same time if you're
good at it other players will want to play with you which you can use as a way to make new friends
they let you exchange items too so that's an easy way to start up conversations with people you don't
know I get it if we play this game with each other we'll have the opportunity to practice our own
making skills I'm not gonna make it any dirtier than you are wrong are you listening to me now
bring your own PSP and then we can all go monster hunting together you got it sure why not and so
the following Monday you guys have both practiced using this thing right yeah yep I was busy this
weekend but I found some time to mess around with it not for very long but you know how it is such as
the life of me milk cow Kodaka what level are you ranked I'm at level one I can't seem to kill any of
the bad guys I'm a level three three already I'm six is that good six yeah that's good it's the highest
level seriously how perfect can one girl get I'm even a prodigy at video games I thought you said
you didn't spend that much time on it how much messing with it did you do not that much I was barely on
it at all let me see for myself neat Zax hey give that back I didn't say you could look at it are you
kidding me you were on it for 53 hours I have to admit it your outfits pretty cute too cute for a
lying show-off like you look at that you've got nasty bags in your eyes I do not I don't get bags I
know exactly what you're up to meet you played the game the entire weekend didn't you a tigress
devotes herself to anything she does even stupid games tigress tigress okay that's right now let's
play the damn thing I don't mind hosting I'll even help you two out by taking us on an easy quest so
you won't she may be another completely crazy chick but at least she's serious about the club are you guys
ready cuz I'm ready sorry that took so long what the hell are you wearing leave me alone I'm just a
beginner I can't help it okay that's no excuse for your entire character it's pathetic he doesn't
even look like you don't take it personal but everything we're looking at is a disaster even
your name is cheesy when is Hawk ever a good idea you guys shut up this is just a game so it can be a
little different from reality come on let's go a hunting looks like we'll get through this level
quickly I wonder what I should kill this time oh silly me I guess I just mixed up all of those
buttons oh well now get it together so we can go a hunting something tells me a player with her rank
doesn't get the buttons mixed up she probably spent all those hours playing for that one moment it was a
stupid mistake I'm not surprised shall we go
yay
what the hell was that about oopsie got my buttons mixed up
whatever you so did that on purpose I so did not you need to relax me paranoia does not look good on you
that's it look out here it comes
oh don't worry I'll take care of this guy
huh I'm not about to let some dumb lizard take me down get ready because I
hey that was a sleepy potion
uh what are you doing
guess
awesome totally killed it and hit me yeah I was trying to give you a little backup I guess I just
don't know my own strength my you were trying to hit me on purpose hey we're supposed to cooperate on
this game so maybe we should try that hmm yeah hooters but I'll make sure to cooperate even more next time well in that case brace yourself I'm gonna cooperate the hell out of this after that the real hunting began
those meat flaps of yours are grossing me out I better turn them into ground beef
shriek away little harpy shriek you won't be saying much when I kill you
silence meat no because I do what I want
cool I found dog right I rock
oh
that doesn't even makes sense
Oh
Oh, sorry guys. I just died
It's like I only really feel alive, but I'm really killing something
Maybe video games aren't right for us
Yeah, seems like a waste of time, right for real and since when did PSPs become like all about the multiplayer games anyway
Why should I have to play with people who are just gonna die on me?
I thought playing with people was the whole point. I completely agree. I don't have a lot of time
Why should I have to share it and with a stranger? Yeah, totally
Yeah, why would you think of anyone else besides you?
Nothing never mind
What do you want to do today same thing we do every day try and take over the world?
How far did you get in monster hunting? I didn't bring forth Imperial wrath, but I did kill Jinro
I also got a ton of tails
Here goes. Do you have anything extra you can share with me? Probably. Hey, uh guys
So I've been playing that monster hunting game, too
Do you by chance have the scarf of DOS Jagira and would you be willing to trade for it?
Sure, whatever you want. Yeah, anything else you need say the word. It's yours. It's no big deal at all
Thanks guys
That's cool by the following day the rumor had spread through the whole school. I had pulled a shakedown in homeroom in broad daylight
Okay, what's that your blonde is showing again there are two modern conveniences known as a television and a gaming console
They use electricity. Yeah, that's not what I meant. Why did you bring them here?
What are they doing in the club room? Um, to play a game with?
How do you even get the TV in here?
Anyway, why would you want to bring them to school to play in the first place?
I found a game that's one not a piece of crap like Monster Hunter and two look useful to us
So I figured I'd bring it in
Be grateful you ingrates shut up coconuts. You're ruining my coffee. Hey, that's not coffee. It's tea and it's also not yours
Sparkling school life
Seven sounds like one of those chick games to me. It's a game about making new friends stupid
So it is this could be good for us to practice casual conversations
Yeah, it's for guys to meet girls though
Didn't they have one for you all to practice meeting hot dudes to be friends with? Why?
What would be the point of being friends with guys? Right. Thank you
All right
I
Excuse me. Why the crap do we have to use your nasty name?
Hmm? I mean, I'm the public face of this club. We should be using my name
You're the club's public face. Well, that explains why no one's joining
Uh, the main character is a guy. So maybe we should use my name? Hell no. Well, at least they're agreeing on something
Fine. Senna is the one who brought the game here for us. I think we should just go ahead and use her name this time
Whatever way to use your head Kodaka. Okay, Kashiwazaki
Sorry change my mind
There
You're such a jerk ass
Hi, I'm Simiponame Kashiwazaki
Oh
What the hell is Simiponame?
Come on. I think it's a lovely random name
You should change your real name to that
Seriously, Senna makes me want to puke like every time I say it
Dude! Simiponame!
This guy's name is Masaru Suzuki. We've been best friends since middle school
What? You're kidding me. This douche already has a best friend and that selfish son of a bitch has the balls to say he wants even more
Stop making that creepy face and move out of the way
The best way to have the best time in high school is to cozy up next to a pretty girl. Go get one
That guy's a player, but he is so right
I'd love to have a pretty friend to cozy up to
Hello, nice to meet you. My name is Akari Fujibayashi
I was nervous about starting this new school, but I am now happy that I'm sitting next to such a nice-looking guy
Would you like to be my friend at this time Simiponame?
Oh, so you get to choose how the guy answers
Number three. How come three? Doesn't that seem rude?
No, not when some hussy you don't know tries to get all up on your stuff on the first day of school
You can't trust girls like that true
I bet she probably says the exact same thing to every single guy in the classroom
Oh, come on. She doesn't look that bad to me
Of course she doesn't
Bitches never look like bitches at first
But there's one of her in every class
She looks so innocent, but all she's really doing is playing every guy in school
Is there one of her in our class?
Totally
Online it says practically every high school girl is a big bitch these days
Surely she realizes she qualifies as a high school girl
Okay, number three it is
What a pushy broad. Get lost
Oh my, I'm so sorry
As it is our first time meeting, I may have been too forward
I will be more careful from now on, so I hope that you are not mad at me
Akari, I'm so sorry
So basically you get to decide what you want to do
And if you make the right choice you get to talk to girls
This game is a rough place for a guy who can't get enough merit points to get a girl to go out with them
It's just like reality
He needs to get good grades so no one thinks he's stupid
Let's start with making him study
Good idea
I hate boys who are cerebrally challenged
The more he studies the smarter he gets
Wow, how big of an idiot was this dude to start out with
Give the poor guy a break it's just a game
Look, someone's here
Oh, I am sorry
Another choice
I bet they go with two
So which one is it?
Number one
Seriously?
Instead of wasting time reading random books
He needs to be focused on studying
I'm aiming for 200 academic points by the next test
So no screwing around, loser
Naturally
No, I'm sorry
You are kind, thank you
May I have your name if you don't mind too much?
Sure
I'm Semoponame Kashiwazaki from class D
Semoponame Kashiwazaki
That is a very nice name
Geez, talk about having terrible taste
It's scary
For now, I'm thinking we ought to be friends with this girl
Are you okay with that?
Yeah, she's way better than that Fujibayashi bitch
Go ahead
Then she's fine
Mom?
Uh-huh.
Yukiko.
Yes?
She's so cute, I can't stand it.
And she likes me.
Is there anything better in the world than having a girl like you?
Yeah.
Plus, she looks like she's a good person.
Yukiko, let's walk home together.
I... no.
I am sorry.
I don't understand. What's wrong with Yukiko?
I guess this was the reason Yukiko Nagata suddenly became so cold.
What? Tell me.
You know how every time you saw that Aukari girl you were really mean to her?
Apparently that caused a nasty rumor to go through school.
A rumor saying that you're mean to girls and therefore not to be trusted.
So basically the reason Yukiko doesn't like me
is because that stupid bitch Aukari has been bad-mouthing me all over the whole damn school?
I hate her so freaking much!
I think you might be exaggerating.
It says here if you get a bad rep, you need to find out who doesn't like you and apologize.
What?
Why the hell would I ever apologize to such an awful person?
This is ridiculous.
I don't even want to be friends with that disgusting cow in the first place.
Totally agree.
How is this our fault that we need to say we're sorry?
By no means am I about to bow down to some idiotic female who's just talking trash
because she got shot down for acting slutty.
Yeah, like for real, right?
I refuse to give in on this.
You and I have total faith that Yukiko will understand anyway.
Yukiko, please, I...
I am sorry.
Goodbye forever!
Wait!
No!
I had faith in her, but she still let me down.
She's really crying.
Why do I only get the crazies?
Hey, where are you off to, Yozara?
To find Akari Fujibayashi and kill her.
Are you okay?
You can go on!
Good morning.
Hi.
How are you doing today?
Hey, Kodaka.
Hmm?
Over here.
Here.
Uh...
I'm letting you borrow that, so be sure and play it as soon as you get home.
And definitely watch out for the third-year event with Akari Fujibayashi.
It's particularly moving.
Akari?
But isn't she the poor girl you kept calling a stupid bitch yet?
No.
I'm sorry.
Listen.
She's been through...
Well, a lot since her parents were killed.
That girl's the strongest girl I know.
She won't let anything get her down.
The only thing in her heart is a ball of love.
Is that so?
Oh!
You have to make sure you capture Yukiko.
Actually, Miho, Natsumi, Mizuki, and Karen, they're all amazing girls.
Okay.
So after going home yesterday, you caught up with her.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So after going home yesterday, you conquered all of them?
Obviously.
Be sure you pay close attention to how they all end, too.
You got that?
Sure.
I'll give it a whirl if I'm in the mood to play it.
No way.
You will play it whether you're in the mood or not.
You have to.
It's an experience everyone should be a part of.
It's not just a game.
It's a work of art.
Don't you understand?
It's life.
Held in your hand.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna be late.
And you better play it.
Oh, crap.
Neighbors Club Record.
Senna became friends with seven different girls,
all of whom are two-dimensional.
It's a rareастиä.
It's a 옆usion to me.
Yeah, that's true, man.
There'll be another lawyer.
Well, I do not use anything…
No.
In my opinion, I can break that out.
You need your head and a bit.
To do that.
It's couldn't.
There are people who need Jelly.
Song of?
Say, level 1.
No, you incluyendoärkeery.
What's wrong?
Hang on with your life.
I really don't know who is working today.
We don't know who is running right now.
But we're going on.
It's a case where the act of performance is working throughout our action.
Myśli terms are already working.
So once the guy found aוג are done,
Yeah, I see theouflower.
Hey, boob face, about those chick gangs.
Did you know people who play them in the middle of the night get brainwashed?
What? They do?
Yep, their brainwaves end up getting controlled by the game,
and they lose their normal sense of judgment,
which means they never make any friends.
That is not true!
On top of that, their hair turns a gross blonde color,
and the fat on their chest expands, turning them into cows.
Is that for real?
Of course not.
You're stupid!
Says the idiot.
Next, there are no flags at the swimming pool.
Why pool?
Can you let your day down показ?
Morning?
Love spring?
Never shoulders bob to fly.
Relax by snapping songs,
ans to fall.
Never Corona pranic.
But the spirits still find spaceones.
Yes.
You cannot just cry.
».
– Slow down!
There's a rush!
Does the mind look like!
akahine?
It's never was commanded by rain.
He does not cry.
You can't cry.
They're not nazi Assistance.
You can rest on the ray.
But that's changed his identity.
Your body feels all your motion
.